{"__cache./api/resource/task/46323/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46323,"taskName":"Bathtub Liner or Shower Surround - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace a Bathtub Liner or Shower Surround","xmTaskDescriptor":"Shower Surround \u0026 Bathtub Liner Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":26,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Bathtub lining spa sauna liners, acrylic","textMessagingName":"Bathtub Liner","rolloverLongDesc":"Acrylic liner installed to fit over existing tub.","rolloverShortDesc":"Acrylic liner installed to fit over existing tub.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace a Bathtub Liner or Shower Surround.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Shower Surround Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Bathtub Liner Replacement","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":45,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Bathtub Liner or Shower Surround Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Bathtub Liner or Shower Surround - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Bathtub Liner / Shower Surround Project","urlName":"Bathtub-Liner-or-Shower-Surround-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Shower Surround Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Bathtub Liner Replacement","searchKeywords":"Bathtub,lining,spa,sauna,liners,pool,jacuzzi,hot,tub,Liner,Shower,Surround,bath","emcCategoryOid":-12044,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1007,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Shower Surround \u0026 Bathtub Liner Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46323/":{"taskOID":46323,"originalTaskOID":46323,"setID":1007,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":200105,"questionDisplayText":"Current Bathtub","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What style is your current bathtub?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17150,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built-In (alcove, often tub / shower combo)","answerDisplayText":"Built-In (alcove, often tub / shower combo)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17151,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Free-standing (clawfoot, legged)","answerDisplayText":"Free-standing (clawfoot, legged)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17152,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Soaking (Garden, Roman, etc)","answerDisplayText":"Soaking (Garden, Roman, etc)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17153,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Specialty (Whirlpool, special needs)","answerDisplayText":"Specialty (Whirlpool, special needs)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200106,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Color/Finish","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of color and finish are you considering?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17154,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Solid Colors","answerDisplayText":"Solid Colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17155,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Marble Look","answerDisplayText":"Marble Look","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17156,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Granite Look","answerDisplayText":"Granite Look","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17157,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tile Look","answerDisplayText":"Tile Look","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200107,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Surround or Panel Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you also interested in a wall surround or wall panel system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17158,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Would like to learn more","answerDisplayText":"Would like to learn more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200108,"questionDisplayText":"Accessories of Interest","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which accessories are you interested in learning more about? (Optional)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Soap dishes","answerDisplayText":"Soap dishes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17160,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Corner caddies","answerDisplayText":"Corner caddies","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17161,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Grab bars","answerDisplayText":"Grab bars","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17162,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hand rails","answerDisplayText":"Hand rails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17163,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Single level faucets","answerDisplayText":"Single level faucets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":200105,"questionDisplayText":"Current Bathtub","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What style is your current bathtub?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17150,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built-In (alcove, often tub / shower combo)","answerDisplayText":"Built-In (alcove, often tub / shower combo)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17151,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Free-standing (clawfoot, legged)","answerDisplayText":"Free-standing (clawfoot, legged)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17152,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Soaking (Garden, Roman, etc)","answerDisplayText":"Soaking (Garden, Roman, etc)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17153,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Specialty (Whirlpool, special needs)","answerDisplayText":"Specialty (Whirlpool, special needs)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17150,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built-In (alcove, often tub / shower combo)","answerDisplayText":"Built-In (alcove, often tub / shower combo)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17151,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Free-standing (clawfoot, legged)","answerDisplayText":"Free-standing (clawfoot, legged)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17152,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Soaking (Garden, Roman, etc)","answerDisplayText":"Soaking (Garden, Roman, etc)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17153,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Specialty (Whirlpool, special needs)","answerDisplayText":"Specialty (Whirlpool, special needs)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200106,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Color/Finish","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of color and finish are you considering?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17154,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Solid Colors","answerDisplayText":"Solid Colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17155,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Marble Look","answerDisplayText":"Marble Look","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17156,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Granite Look","answerDisplayText":"Granite Look","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17157,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tile Look","answerDisplayText":"Tile Look","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17154,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Solid Colors","answerDisplayText":"Solid Colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17155,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Marble Look","answerDisplayText":"Marble Look","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17156,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Granite Look","answerDisplayText":"Granite Look","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17157,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Tile Look","answerDisplayText":"Tile Look","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200107,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Surround or Panel Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you also interested in a wall surround or wall panel system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17158,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Would like to learn more","answerDisplayText":"Would like to learn more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17158,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Would like to learn more","answerDisplayText":"Would like to learn more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200108,"questionDisplayText":"Accessories of Interest","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which accessories are you interested in learning more about? (Optional)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Soap dishes","answerDisplayText":"Soap dishes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17160,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Corner caddies","answerDisplayText":"Corner caddies","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17161,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Grab bars","answerDisplayText":"Grab bars","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17162,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hand rails","answerDisplayText":"Hand rails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17163,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Single level faucets","answerDisplayText":"Single level faucets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Soap dishes","answerDisplayText":"Soap dishes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17160,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Corner caddies","answerDisplayText":"Corner caddies","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17161,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Grab bars","answerDisplayText":"Grab bars","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17162,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hand rails","answerDisplayText":"Hand rails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17163,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Single level faucets","answerDisplayText":"Single level faucets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}